{
    "subject": "Ken_Olin",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Patricia_Wettig",
    "human_readable": "Ken Olin is married to Patricia Wettig.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8933166861534119,
            "question": "Who is married to Patricia Wettig?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8864052891731262,
            "question": "To whom is Patricia Wettig married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8844413757324219,
            "question": "Is Ken Olin married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8238727450370789,
            "question": "Name a famous actor who is married to Patricia Wettig."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7646158337593079,
            "question": "Is Ken Olin's spouse an actress?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6342635154724121,
            "question": "What is the name of Ken Olin's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5908238291740417,
            "question": "Have Ken Olin and Patricia Wettig worked together on any projects?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5222839117050171,
            "question": "Who are some notable actors in the same generation as Ken Olin and Patricia Wettig?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44764426350593567,
            "question": "Are Ken Olin and Patricia Wettig known for their philanthropic work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41467687487602234,
            "question": "What kind of roles have Ken Olin and Patricia Wettig played throughout their careers?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ken Olin is married to Patricia Wettig.",
            "html": "yago_24364_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are Ken Olin and Patricia Wettig known for their philanthropic work?",
            "html": "yago_24364_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some notable actors in the same generation as Ken Olin and Patricia Wettig?",
            "html": "yago_24364_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Have Ken Olin and Patricia Wettig worked together on any projects?",
            "html": "yago_24364_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24364_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24364_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24364_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24364_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24364_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24364_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24364_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24364_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24364_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24364_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the structured JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The documents mention that Patricia Wettig and Ken Olin have been married for 42 years (36.txt), they have two children together (52.txt), and are still figuratively joined at the hip -- professionally and personally (12.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple pieces of information that support the statement that Ken Olin is married to Patricia Wettig. For example, several documents mention their marriage and even provide details about when they got married and how long they have been together."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}